,0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14
"Biomedecine Agency, Saint Denis La Plaine.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99999535, 'word': 'Biomedecine Agency', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999731, 'word': 'Saint Denis La Plaine', 'start': 20, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.92253125, 'word': '.', 'start': 41, 'end': 42}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Project Management Department, Sanwa Kagaku Kenkyusho Co., Ltd., Nagoya, Japan.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9994619, 'word': 'Sanwa Kagaku Kenkyusho Co., Ltd', 'start': 31, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999953, 'word': 'Nagoya', 'start': 65, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999968, 'word': 'Japan', 'start': 73, 'end': 78}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Translational Research Institute, Brisbane, Australia","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99999624, 'word': 'Translational Research Institute', 'start': 0, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997187, 'word': 'Brisbane', 'start': 34, 'end': 42}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999964, 'word': 'Australia', 'start': 44, 'end': 53}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Pediatric Nephrology, State University of Campinas (UNICAMP), Campinas, Brazil.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99356866, 'word': 'Pediatri', 'start': 0, 'end': 8}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8820653, 'word': 'Nephrology', 'start': 10, 'end': 20}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99900264, 'word': 'State University of Campinas', 'start': 22, 'end': 50}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99983144, 'word': 'UNICAMP', 'start': 52, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998826, 'word': 'Campinas', 'start': 62, 'end': 70}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999901, 'word': 'Brazil', 'start': 72, 'end': 78}",,,,,,,,,
"Otsuka Pharmaceutical Development & Commercialization, Princeton, New Jersey.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99984175, 'word': 'Otsuka Pharmaceutical Development & Commercialization', 'start': 0, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998368, 'word': 'Princeton', 'start': 55, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999767, 'word': 'New Jersey', 'start': 66, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96053845, 'word': '.', 'start': 76, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,,,,
"AMGA (American Medical Group Association), Alexandria, Virginia and OptumLabs Visiting Fellow.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999926, 'word': 'AMGA', 'start': 0, 'end': 4}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99998623, 'word': 'American Medical Group Association', 'start': 6, 'end': 40}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999873, 'word': 'Alexandria', 'start': 43, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999297, 'word': 'Virginia', 'start': 55, 'end': 63}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99997735, 'word': 'OptumLabs', 'start': 68, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology, Clinique Sainte Anne, Strasbourg, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.95557946, 'word': 'Department of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96063685, 'word': 'Clinique Sainte Anne', 'start': 26, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998116, 'word': 'Strasbourg', 'start': 48, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999998, 'word': 'France', 'start': 60, 'end': 66}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology, Hôpital Européen Georges Pompidou, Assistance Publique-Hôpitaux de Paris, Paris","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.59010756, 'word': 'Department', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.80283415, 'word': 'Nephrology', 'start': 14, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.8959354, 'word': 'Hôpital Européen Georges Pompidou', 'start': 26, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9514005, 'word': 'Assistance Publique-Hôpitaux de Paris', 'start': 61, 'end': 98}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999404, 'word': 'Paris', 'start': 100, 'end': 105}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, San Francisco, California.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9997886, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998283, 'word': 'San Francisco', 'start': 24, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'California', 'start': 39, 'end': 49}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Pathology, Hôpital Maisonneuve-Rosemont, Université de Montréal, Montréal, Québec, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7756598, 'word': 'Division', 'start': 0, 'end': 8}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.77807117, 'word': 'Pathology', 'start': 12, 'end': 21}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9800355, 'word': 'al Maisonneuve-Rosemont', 'start': 28, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9916917, 'word': 'Université de Montréal', 'start': 53, 'end': 75}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999972, 'word': 'Montréal', 'start': 77, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998426, 'word': 'Québec', 'start': 87, 'end': 93}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999154, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 95, 'end': 101}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Pediatrics, University Hospital of Split, Split, Croatia.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.72229046, 'word': 'Pediatri', 'start': 14, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.98675835, 'word': 'University Hospital of Split', 'start': 26, 'end': 54}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999876, 'word': 'Split', 'start': 56, 'end': 61}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999992, 'word': 'Croatia', 'start': 63, 'end': 70}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, Division of Nephrology and Hypertension and Department of Transplantation Medicine, New York Presbyterian Hospital-Weill Cornell Medical Center, New York, NY.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99209976, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99484277, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology and Hypertension', 'start': 24, 'end': 63}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99246556, 'word': 'Department of Transplantation Medicine', 'start': 68, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.97604686, 'word': 'New York Presbyterian Hospital-Weill Cornell Medical Center', 'start': 108, 'end': 167}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998534, 'word': 'New York', 'start': 169, 'end': 177}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9995314, 'word': 'NY', 'start': 179, 'end': 181}",,,,,,,,,
"Centre de Référence des Maladies Rénales Rares, Hôpital Femme Mère Enfant, Lyon, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99327904, 'word': 'Centre de Référence des Maladies Rénales Rares', 'start': 0, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9896071, 'word': 'Hôpital Femme Mère Enfant', 'start': 48, 'end': 73}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999985, 'word': 'Lyon', 'start': 75, 'end': 79}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999963, 'word': 'France', 'start': 81, 'end': 87}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.85291654, 'word': '.', 'start': 87, 'end': 88}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Molecular and Clinical Medicine, Institute of Medicine, Sahlgrenska Academy, University of Gothenburg, Gothenburg, Sweden.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9948094, 'word': 'Department of Molecular and Clinical Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 45}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99958855, 'word': 'Institute of Medicine', 'start': 47, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9996363, 'word': 'Sahlgrenska Academy', 'start': 70, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9916003, 'word': 'University of Gothenburg', 'start': 91, 'end': 115}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'Gothenburg', 'start': 117, 'end': 127}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999547, 'word': 'Sweden', 'start': 129, 'end': 135}",,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9990208, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99992174, 'word': 'Yale University', 'start': 24, 'end': 39}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999852, 'word': 'New Haven', 'start': 41, 'end': 50}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999829, 'word': 'Connecticut', 'start': 52, 'end': 63}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Renal-Electrolyte and Hypertension Division, Perelman School of Medicine, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9706884, 'word': 'Renal-Electrolyte and Hypertension Division', 'start': 0, 'end': 43}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.63480616, 'word': 'Pere', 'start': 45, 'end': 49}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.66385895, 'word': 'lman School', 'start': 49, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.65137726, 'word': 'Medicine', 'start': 64, 'end': 72}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99968386, 'word': 'University of Pennsylvania', 'start': 74, 'end': 100}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.95597523, 'word': 'Philadelphia', 'start': 102, 'end': 114}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9997297, 'word': 'Pennsylvania', 'start': 116, 'end': 128}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996066, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 130, 'end': 133}",,,,,,,
"Ludwig Boltzmann Institute for Osteology at the Hanusch Hospital of OEGK and AUVA Trauma Centre Meidling, 1st Medical Department, Hanusch Hospital, Vienna, Austria.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9974353, 'word': 'Ludwig Boltzmann Institute for Osteology', 'start': 0, 'end': 40}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99994475, 'word': 'Hanusch Hospital', 'start': 48, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99960476, 'word': 'OEGK', 'start': 68, 'end': 72}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8397085, 'word': 'AUVA Traum', 'start': 77, 'end': 87}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.66743547, 'word': 'id', 'start': 98, 'end': 100}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996364, 'word': 'Hanusch Hospital', 'start': 130, 'end': 146}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999607, 'word': 'Vienna', 'start': 148, 'end': 154}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999969, 'word': 'Austria', 'start': 156, 'end': 163}",,,,,,,
"Institute of Pathology, University Hospital Tübingen, Tübingen, Germany.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99852216, 'word': 'Institute of Pathology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.81668174, 'word': 'University Hospital Tübingen', 'start': 24, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999094, 'word': 'Tübingen', 'start': 54, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999957, 'word': 'Germany', 'start': 64, 'end': 71}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, University of Hong Kong, Queen Mary Hospital, Pokfulam, Hong Kong.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.95238954, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99985653, 'word': 'University of Hong Kong', 'start': 24, 'end': 47}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999932, 'word': 'Queen Mary Hospital', 'start': 49, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99993634, 'word': 'Pokfulam', 'start': 70, 'end': 78}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999714, 'word': 'Hong Kong', 'start': 80, 'end': 89}",,,,,,,,,,
"Ajmera Transplant Centre, University Health Network, Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Electronic address: istvan.mucsi@utoronto.ca.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.93142223, 'word': 'Ajmera Transplant Centre', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7271347, 'word': 'University Health Network', 'start': 26, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999578, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 53, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999796, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 62, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999912, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 71, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9998009, 'word': 'istvan', 'start': 99, 'end': 105}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99929047, 'word': 'mucsi', 'start': 106, 'end': 111}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9918504, 'word': 'utoronto', 'start': 112, 'end': 120}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.88045377, 'word': 'ca', 'start': 121, 'end': 123}",,,,,,
"Department of Obstetrics and Gynecology, Xijing Hospital, The Fourth Military Medical University, Xi'an, People's Republic of China.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.888344, 'word': 'Department of Obstetrics and Gynecology', 'start': 0, 'end': 39}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998632, 'word': 'Xijing Hospital', 'start': 41, 'end': 56}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.74378425, 'word': 'The Fourth Military Medical University', 'start': 58, 'end': 96}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999898, 'word': ""Xi'an"", 'start': 98, 'end': 103}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999768, 'word': ""People's Republic of China"", 'start': 105, 'end': 131}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Obstetrics, Gynecology and Reproductive Medicine, Hopital Foch, Suresnes, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99439657, 'word': 'Department of Obstetrics, Gynecology and Reproductive Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.744015, 'word': 'Hopital Foch', 'start': 64, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999543, 'word': 'Suresnes', 'start': 78, 'end': 86}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999714, 'word': 'France', 'start': 88, 'end': 94}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Internal Medicine, College of Medicine, Institute of Kidney Disease Research, Yonsei University, Seoul.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9980944, 'word': 'Department of Internal Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 31}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99728113, 'word': 'College of Medicine', 'start': 33, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999809, 'word': 'Institute of Kidney Disease Research', 'start': 54, 'end': 90}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999984, 'word': 'Yonsei University', 'start': 92, 'end': 109}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998677, 'word': 'Seoul', 'start': 111, 'end': 116}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8466313, 'word': '.', 'start': 116, 'end': 117}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Regenerative Medicine Research, Texas Heart Institute, Houston, TX.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999717, 'word': 'Department of Regenerative Medicine Research', 'start': 0, 'end': 44}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999356, 'word': 'Texas Heart Institute', 'start': 46, 'end': 67}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999972, 'word': 'Houston', 'start': 69, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99942976, 'word': 'TX', 'start': 78, 'end': 80}",,,,,,,,,,,
"LIM 12, Faculdade de Medicina da Universidade de São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5677141, 'word': 'LIM', 'start': 0, 'end': 3}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999, 'word': 'Faculdade de Medicina da Universidade de São Paulo', 'start': 8, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999877, 'word': 'São Paulo', 'start': 60, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999862, 'word': 'Brazil', 'start': 71, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Multi-Organ Transplant Program, Ajmera Transplant Center, University of Toronto, Toronto, ON, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9986644, 'word': 'Multi-Organ Transplant Program', 'start': 0, 'end': 30}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9899826, 'word': 'Ajmera Transplant Center', 'start': 32, 'end': 56}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9874014, 'word': 'University of Toronto', 'start': 58, 'end': 79}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999695, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 81, 'end': 88}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.997917, 'word': 'ON', 'start': 90, 'end': 92}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999826, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 94, 'end': 100}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, Cedars-Sinai Medical Center, Los Angeles, California, USA.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.5207893, 'word': 'Department', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.48376596, 'word': 'of', 'start': 11, 'end': 13}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.6633857, 'word': 'Medicine', 'start': 14, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9908408, 'word': 'Cedars-Sinai Medical Center', 'start': 24, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999505, 'word': 'Los Angeles', 'start': 53, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997246, 'word': 'California', 'start': 66, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999627, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 78, 'end': 81}",,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology-Hypertension, University of California San Diego, San Diego, California.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9997859, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology-Hypertension', 'start': 0, 'end': 35}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99992055, 'word': 'University of California San Diego', 'start': 37, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998903, 'word': 'San Diego', 'start': 73, 'end': 82}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999908, 'word': 'California', 'start': 84, 'end': 94}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.983613, 'word': '.', 'start': 94, 'end': 95}",,,,,,,,,,
"Université de Paris Cité, INSERM, PARCC, Paris Institute for Transplantation and Organ Regeneration, Paris, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99995404, 'word': 'Université de Paris Cité', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999838, 'word': 'INSERM', 'start': 26, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999229, 'word': 'PARCC', 'start': 34, 'end': 39}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99954283, 'word': 'Paris Institute for Transplantation and Organ Regeneration', 'start': 41, 'end': 99}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999956, 'word': 'Paris', 'start': 101, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999654, 'word': 'France', 'start': 108, 'end': 114}",,,,,,,,,
"Unit of Infectious Diseases, Division of General Pediatrics, Department of Pediatrics, Gynecology and Obstetrics, Geneva University Hospitals and University of Geneva, Geneva, Switzerland.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9749551, 'word': 'Unit of Infectious Diseases', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9986993, 'word': 'Division of General Pediatrics', 'start': 29, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9988632, 'word': 'Department of Pediatrics, Gynecology and Obstetrics', 'start': 61, 'end': 112}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6231805, 'word': 'Gene', 'start': 114, 'end': 118}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.50822484, 'word': 'va', 'start': 118, 'end': 120}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.82816166, 'word': 'University Hospitals', 'start': 121, 'end': 141}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99982274, 'word': 'University of Geneva', 'start': 146, 'end': 166}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999926, 'word': 'Geneva', 'start': 168, 'end': 174}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999404, 'word': 'Switzerland', 'start': 176, 'end': 187}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5117121, 'word': '.', 'start': 187, 'end': 188}",,,,,
"Department of Pediatric Nephrology, Hôpital des Enfants, CHU Toulouse, Toulouse, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.93626714, 'word': 'Department of Pediatric Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9979204, 'word': 'Hôpital des Enfants', 'start': 36, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8914147, 'word': 'CHU Toulouse', 'start': 57, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999, 'word': 'Toulouse', 'start': 71, 'end': 79}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999963, 'word': 'France', 'start': 81, 'end': 87}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Microbiology, Immunology and Transplantation, KU Leuven, Leuven, Belgium.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99984866, 'word': 'Department of Microbiology, Immunology and Transplantation', 'start': 0, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999925, 'word': 'KU Leuven', 'start': 60, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999933, 'word': 'Leuven', 'start': 71, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999919, 'word': 'Belgium', 'start': 79, 'end': 86}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8886165, 'word': '.', 'start': 86, 'end': 87}",,,,,,,,,,
"INSERM U1151, service des explorations fonctionnelles hôpital Necker-Enfants Malades, DMU Biophygen, GHU Centre Université de Paris APHP. Paris, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998782, 'word': 'INSERM', 'start': 0, 'end': 6}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9696816, 'word': 'Necker-Enfants Malades', 'start': 62, 'end': 84}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9128033, 'word': 'DMU Biophygen', 'start': 86, 'end': 99}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9883814, 'word': 'GHU Centre Université de Paris APHP', 'start': 101, 'end': 136}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999918, 'word': 'Paris', 'start': 138, 'end': 143}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999962, 'word': 'France', 'start': 145, 'end': 151}",,,,,,,,,
"Istituto di Ricerche Farmacologiche Mario Negri IRCCS, Clinical Research Center for Rare Diseases Aldo e Cele Daccò, Ranica, Italy.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99997383, 'word': 'Istituto di Ricerche Farmacologiche Mario Negri IRCCS', 'start': 0, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9964098, 'word': 'Clinical Research Center for Rare Diseases Aldo e Cele Daccò', 'start': 55, 'end': 115}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996924, 'word': 'Ranica', 'start': 117, 'end': 123}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999914, 'word': 'Italy', 'start': 125, 'end': 130}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, University of Alabama at Birmingham and VA Birmingham Health Care, Birmingham, Alabama.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998571, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99964505, 'word': 'University of Alabama at Birmingham', 'start': 24, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.85665196, 'word': 'VA Birmingham Health Care', 'start': 64, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999826, 'word': 'Birmingham', 'start': 91, 'end': 101}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998784, 'word': 'Alabama', 'start': 103, 'end': 110}",,,,,,,,,,
"University of Alabama at Birmingham, Heersink School of Medicine, Birmingham, Alabama, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9993006, 'word': 'University of Alabama at Birmingham', 'start': 0, 'end': 35}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.97627133, 'word': 'Heersink School of Medicine', 'start': 37, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996054, 'word': 'Birmingham', 'start': 66, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999825, 'word': 'Alabama', 'start': 78, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999795, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 87, 'end': 90}",,,,,,,,,,
"Clinical Research Academy, Peking University Shenzhen Hospital, Peking University, Shenzhen, China","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999753, 'word': 'Clinical Research Academy', 'start': 0, 'end': 25}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.992656, 'word': 'Peking University Shenzhen Hospital', 'start': 27, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9921249, 'word': 'Peking University', 'start': 64, 'end': 81}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999887, 'word': 'Shenzhen', 'start': 83, 'end': 91}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999523, 'word': 'China', 'start': 93, 'end': 98}",,,,,,,,,,
"Ajmera Transplant Centre, University Health Network, Toronto, Ontario, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.689783, 'word': 'Ajmera', 'start': 0, 'end': 6}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.51040053, 'word': 'Transplant Centre', 'start': 7, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.7375337, 'word': 'University', 'start': 26, 'end': 36}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6573851, 'word': 'Health Network', 'start': 37, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999727, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 53, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998665, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 62, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 71, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Department of Medicine, Hamilton Health Sciences Centre, McMaster University, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9197972, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.85166574, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 24, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99108505, 'word': 'Hamilton Health Sciences Centre', 'start': 48, 'end': 79}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9747777, 'word': 'McMaster University', 'start': 81, 'end': 100}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997365, 'word': 'Hamilton', 'start': 102, 'end': 110}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997723, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 112, 'end': 119}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999907, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 121, 'end': 127}",,,,,,,,
"School of Public Health, The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston, Houston, Texas.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9729231, 'word': 'School of Public Health', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.87730414, 'word': 'University of Texas Health Science Center at', 'start': 29, 'end': 73}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9231458, 'word': 'Houston', 'start': 74, 'end': 81}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999782, 'word': 'Houston', 'start': 83, 'end': 90}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999691, 'word': 'Texas', 'start': 92, 'end': 97}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Transplantation, Department of Surgery, University of California, San Francisco, California, USA. Electronic address: qizhi.tang@ucsf.edu.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99911565, 'word': 'Division of Transplantation', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9980714, 'word': 'Department of Surgery', 'start': 29, 'end': 50}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998289, 'word': 'University of California', 'start': 52, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99858606, 'word': 'San Francisco', 'start': 78, 'end': 91}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998343, 'word': 'California', 'start': 93, 'end': 103}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999821, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 105, 'end': 108}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99767077, 'word': 'qizhi', 'start': 130, 'end': 135}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99918634, 'word': 'tang', 'start': 136, 'end': 140}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99838525, 'word': 'ucsf', 'start': 141, 'end': 145}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7355196, 'word': 'edu', 'start': 146, 'end': 149}",,,,,
"Department of Immunology, Transplant Medicine and Internal Diseases, Medical University of Warsaw, Warsaw, Poland.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9997376, 'word': 'Department of Immunology, Transplant Medicine and Internal Diseases', 'start': 0, 'end': 67}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99991673, 'word': 'Medical University of Warsaw', 'start': 69, 'end': 97}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999948, 'word': 'Warsaw', 'start': 99, 'end': 105}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999962, 'word': 'Poland', 'start': 107, 'end': 113}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8946075, 'word': '.', 'start': 113, 'end': 114}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Oncology, University of Alberta, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99789923, 'word': 'Department of Oncology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99992585, 'word': 'University of Alberta', 'start': 24, 'end': 45}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999344, 'word': 'Edmonton', 'start': 47, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996716, 'word': 'Alberta', 'start': 57, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 66, 'end': 72}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Abdominal Transplantation, Department of Surgery and Perioperative Care, Dell Medical School at the University of Texas at Austin, Austin, Texas, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.98667127, 'word': 'Division of Abdominal Transplantation', 'start': 0, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.94386977, 'word': 'Department of Surgery and Perioperative Care', 'start': 39, 'end': 83}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.8687951, 'word': 'Dell Medical School', 'start': 85, 'end': 104}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9981669, 'word': 'University of Texas at Austin', 'start': 112, 'end': 141}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99995935, 'word': 'Austin', 'start': 143, 'end': 149}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99995995, 'word': 'Texas', 'start': 151, 'end': 156}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99994874, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 158, 'end': 161}",,,,,,,,
"National Clinical Research Center for Kidney Disease, State Key Laboratory of Organ Failure Research, Nanfang Hospital, Southern Medical University. Electronic address: ffhouguangzhou@163.com.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999941, 'word': 'National Clinical Research Center for Kidney Disease', 'start': 0, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998371, 'word': 'State Key Laboratory of Organ Failure Research', 'start': 54, 'end': 100}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998856, 'word': 'Nanfang Hospital', 'start': 102, 'end': 118}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6300072, 'word': 'Southern Medical University', 'start': 120, 'end': 147}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.59145063, 'word': 'ho', 'start': 171, 'end': 173}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.5920216, 'word': 'zhou', 'start': 179, 'end': 183}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.667112, 'word': '.', 'start': 187, 'end': 188}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Infectious Diseases, Ramón y Cajal University Hospital, Madrid, Spain.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.88159585, 'word': 'Department of Infec', 'start': 0, 'end': 19}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.93093985, 'word': 'us Diseases', 'start': 22, 'end': 33}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9994397, 'word': 'Ramón y Cajal University Hospital', 'start': 35, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999926, 'word': 'Madrid', 'start': 70, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999726, 'word': 'Spain', 'start': 78, 'end': 83}",,,,,,,,,,
"Life Sciences Institute, Zhejiang University, Hangzhou, People's Republic of China.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'Life Sciences Institute', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999813, 'word': 'Zhejiang University', 'start': 25, 'end': 44}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999917, 'word': 'Hangzhou', 'start': 46, 'end': 54}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996513, 'word': ""People's Republic of China"", 'start': 56, 'end': 82}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.87028354, 'word': '.', 'start': 82, 'end': 83}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology, CH Pontoise, Pontoise, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9981105, 'word': 'Department of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.95992255, 'word': 'CH Pontoise', 'start': 26, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998516, 'word': 'Pontoise', 'start': 39, 'end': 47}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999726, 'word': 'France', 'start': 49, 'end': 55}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Institute of Medical Immunology, Virchow - Klinikum, Berlin, Germany. Electronic address: birgit.sawitzki@bih-charite.de.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99998486, 'word': 'Institute of Medical Immunology', 'start': 0, 'end': 31}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99428713, 'word': 'Virchow', 'start': 33, 'end': 40}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9980072, 'word': 'Klinikum', 'start': 43, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'Berlin', 'start': 53, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999962, 'word': 'Germany', 'start': 61, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9300049, 'word': 'birgit.sawitzki', 'start': 90, 'end': 105}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9377654, 'word': 'bih-charite.de.', 'start': 106, 'end': 121}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Internal Medicine, Boramae Medical Center, Seoul, Korea","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9805826, 'word': 'Department of Internal Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 31}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998913, 'word': 'Boramae Medical Center', 'start': 33, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999951, 'word': 'Seoul', 'start': 57, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999995, 'word': 'Korea', 'start': 64, 'end': 69}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Cardiovascular Disease, University of Alabama-Birmingham, Birmingham, Alabama.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9985765, 'word': 'Division of Cardiovascular Disease', 'start': 0, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9815812, 'word': 'University of Alabama-Birmingham', 'start': 36, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9995461, 'word': 'Birmingham', 'start': 70, 'end': 80}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999094, 'word': 'Alabama', 'start': 82, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7385125, 'word': '.', 'start': 89, 'end': 90}",,,,,,,,,,
"Research Institute, Ottawa Hospital, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99998766, 'word': 'Research Institute', 'start': 0, 'end': 18}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998516, 'word': 'Ottawa Hospital', 'start': 20, 'end': 35}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999535, 'word': 'Ottawa', 'start': 37, 'end': 43}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999857, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 45, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999297, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 54, 'end': 60}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology, Hôpital Européen Georges Pompidou, Assistance Publique-Hôpitaux de Paris, Paris.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8357946, 'word': 'Department of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9218025, 'word': 'Hôpital Européen Georges Pompidou', 'start': 26, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.6505173, 'word': 'Assist', 'start': 61, 'end': 67}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.61343575, 'word': 'ance Publique', 'start': 67, 'end': 80}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.7695238, 'word': '-Hôpitaux de Paris', 'start': 80, 'end': 98}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999535, 'word': 'Paris', 'start': 100, 'end': 105}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Internal Medicine, Division of Nephrology and Transplantation, Erasmus Medical Center, Rotterdam, The Netherlands.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99073565, 'word': 'Department of Internal Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 31}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9951255, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology and Transplantation', 'start': 33, 'end': 75}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99774265, 'word': 'Erasmus Medical Center', 'start': 77, 'end': 99}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999552, 'word': 'Rotterdam', 'start': 101, 'end': 110}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999841, 'word': 'The Netherlands', 'start': 112, 'end': 127}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Urology, and Kangbuk Samsung Hospital, School of Medicine, Sungkyunkwan University, Seoul, South Korea.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.95873916, 'word': 'Department of Urology', 'start': 0, 'end': 21}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999175, 'word': 'Kangbuk Samsung Hospital', 'start': 27, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.4314564, 'word': 'School', 'start': 53, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.60315454, 'word': 'of Medicine', 'start': 60, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998736, 'word': 'Sungkyunkwan University', 'start': 73, 'end': 96}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999297, 'word': 'Seoul', 'start': 98, 'end': 103}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999475, 'word': 'South Korea', 'start': 105, 'end': 116}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Hepatobiliary and Liver Transplant Surgery, St. James's University Hospital, Leeds Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust, Leeds, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7075286, 'word': 'Department of Hepatobiliary', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5748089, 'word': 'Live', 'start': 32, 'end': 36}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99985677, 'word': ""St. James's University Hospital"", 'start': 58, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9606043, 'word': 'Leeds Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust', 'start': 91, 'end': 125}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999957, 'word': 'Leeds', 'start': 127, 'end': 132}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999577, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 134, 'end': 148}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology, Limoges University hospital","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.951121, 'word': 'of Nephrology', 'start': 11, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.695619, 'word': 'Limoges University', 'start': 26, 'end': 44}",,,,,,,,,,,,,
"Clinical and Diagnostic Immunology, Department of Microbiology, Immunology and Transplantation, KU Leuven, Leuven","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.77499974, 'word': 'Clinical and Diagnos', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9949169, 'word': 'Immunology', 'start': 24, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9993598, 'word': 'Department of Microbiology, Immunology and Transplantation', 'start': 36, 'end': 94}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999145, 'word': 'KU Leuven', 'start': 96, 'end': 105}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998444, 'word': 'Leuven', 'start': 107, 'end': 113}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of General Internal Medicine, School of Medicine, Duke University, Durham, North Carolina","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9703515, 'word': 'Division of General Internal Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.81609136, 'word': 'School of Medicine', 'start': 39, 'end': 57}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9982239, 'word': 'Duke University', 'start': 59, 'end': 74}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999257, 'word': 'Durham', 'start': 76, 'end': 82}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999907, 'word': 'North Carolina', 'start': 84, 'end': 98}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, Division of Hematology, University of Ottawa, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.997977, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.95086384, 'word': 'Division', 'start': 24, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.94900745, 'word': 'Hematology', 'start': 36, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99948776, 'word': 'University of Ottawa', 'start': 48, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997663, 'word': 'Ottawa', 'start': 70, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997306, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 78, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999919, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 87, 'end': 93}",,,,,,,,
"Nuffield Department of Surgical Sciences, University of Oxford, Oxford, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9768237, 'word': 'Nuffield Department of Surgical Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 40}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99987394, 'word': 'University of Oxford', 'start': 42, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9995548, 'word': 'Oxford', 'start': 64, 'end': 70}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999996, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 72, 'end': 86}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology and Transplantation, University Hospital, Strasbourg.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9961931, 'word': 'Department of Nephrology and Transplantation', 'start': 0, 'end': 44}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9899852, 'word': 'University Hospital', 'start': 46, 'end': 65}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9997328, 'word': 'Strasbourg', 'start': 67, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Thoracic Intensive Care Unit, Foch Hospital, Suresnes, France.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.82237375, 'word': 'Thor', 'start': 0, 'end': 4}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999845, 'word': 'Foch Hospital', 'start': 30, 'end': 43}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999949, 'word': 'Suresnes', 'start': 45, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999968, 'word': 'France', 'start': 55, 'end': 61}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Urology, Shandong Provincial Hospital Affiliated to Shandong First Medical University, Jinan, Shandong, China.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.74661815, 'word': 'Urology', 'start': 14, 'end': 21}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99787486, 'word': 'Shandong Provincial Hospital', 'start': 23, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99577796, 'word': 'Shandong First Medical University', 'start': 66, 'end': 99}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998486, 'word': 'Jinan', 'start': 101, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998844, 'word': 'Shandong', 'start': 108, 'end': 116}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999951, 'word': 'China', 'start': 118, 'end': 123}",,,,,,,,,
"GlaxoSmithKline, Collegeville, PA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999922, 'word': 'GlaxoSmithKline', 'start': 0, 'end': 15}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999531, 'word': 'Collegeville', 'start': 17, 'end': 29}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9996923, 'word': 'PA', 'start': 31, 'end': 33}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Institute of Pathology, Nephropathology Section, University Medical Center Hamburg-Eppendorf, Hamburg, Germany.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9996349, 'word': 'Institute of Pathology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7927683, 'word': 'Nephropathology Section', 'start': 24, 'end': 47}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.89391536, 'word': 'University Medical Center', 'start': 49, 'end': 74}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.95354575, 'word': 'Hamburg-Eppendorf', 'start': 75, 'end': 92}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999639, 'word': 'Hamburg', 'start': 94, 'end': 101}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999939, 'word': 'Germany', 'start': 103, 'end': 110}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Critical Care Medicine, Sunnybrook Health Sciences Center, University of Toronto, Toronto, Ontario, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.62952775, 'word': 'Department of Critic', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.68361044, 'word': 'Care Medicine', 'start': 23, 'end': 36}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99960893, 'word': 'Sunnybrook Health Sciences Center', 'start': 38, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9879658, 'word': 'University of Toronto', 'start': 73, 'end': 94}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998856, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 96, 'end': 103}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999795, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 105, 'end': 112}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998975, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 114, 'end': 120}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Surgery, Atrium Health Wake Forest Baptist, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96197593, 'word': 'Atrium Health Wake', 'start': 23, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.6243376, 'word': 'Forest', 'start': 42, 'end': 48}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8435858, 'word': 'Baptist', 'start': 49, 'end': 56}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999442, 'word': 'Winston-Salem', 'start': 58, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999849, 'word': 'North Carolina', 'start': 73, 'end': 87}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999521, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 89, 'end': 92}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Clinical Chemistry, CIRM, CHU de Liège, University of Liège, Liège, Belgium.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9996497, 'word': 'Department of Clinical Chemistry', 'start': 0, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999152, 'word': 'CIRM', 'start': 34, 'end': 38}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.87297994, 'word': 'CHU de Liège', 'start': 40, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9973515, 'word': 'University of Liège', 'start': 54, 'end': 73}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998665, 'word': 'Liège', 'start': 75, 'end': 80}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999919, 'word': 'Belgium', 'start': 82, 'end': 89}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology, Charité Universitätsmedizin Berlin, Berlin, Germany.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9429948, 'word': 'Department of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9996992, 'word': 'Charité Universitätsmedizin Berlin', 'start': 26, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999864, 'word': 'Berlin', 'start': 62, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999951, 'word': 'Germany', 'start': 70, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Pediatric Nephrology Institute, Rambam Health Care Campus, Haifa, Israel.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99992883, 'word': 'Pediatric Nephrology Institute', 'start': 0, 'end': 30}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99985725, 'word': 'Rambam Health Care Campus', 'start': 32, 'end': 57}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999901, 'word': 'Haifa', 'start': 59, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999464, 'word': 'Israel', 'start': 66, 'end': 72}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, University of California San Francisco, San Francisco, California.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99859524, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998571, 'word': 'University of California San Francisco', 'start': 24, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997103, 'word': 'San Francisco', 'start': 64, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998605, 'word': 'California', 'start': 79, 'end': 89}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology and Transplant, Department of Medicine, Indiana University School of Medicine, Indianapolis, Indiana, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9969883, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology and Transplant', 'start': 0, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9739785, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 39, 'end': 61}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9835197, 'word': 'Indiana University School of Medicine', 'start': 63, 'end': 100}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997365, 'word': 'Indianapolis', 'start': 102, 'end': 114}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999982, 'word': 'Indiana', 'start': 116, 'end': 123}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997234, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 125, 'end': 128}",,,,,,,,,
"Division of Thoracic Surgery, Department of Surgery, University of Toronto, Toronto, Ontario, Canada","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.94726896, 'word': 'Division of Thoracic Surgery', 'start': 0, 'end': 28}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9783553, 'word': 'Department of Surgery', 'start': 30, 'end': 51}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99958754, 'word': 'University of Toronto', 'start': 53, 'end': 74}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997485, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 76, 'end': 83}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996877, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 85, 'end': 92}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998903, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 94, 'end': 100}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Quantitative Health Sciences, Mayo Clinic, Jacksonville, FL.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999525, 'word': 'Department of Quantitative Health Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 42}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.994209, 'word': 'Mayo Clinic', 'start': 44, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999707, 'word': 'Jacksonville', 'start': 57, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99988616, 'word': 'FL', 'start': 71, 'end': 73}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Surgery and Emory Transplant Center, Emory University, Atlanta, Georgia, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99895185, 'word': 'Department of Surgery and Emory Transplant Center', 'start': 0, 'end': 49}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999226, 'word': 'Emory University', 'start': 51, 'end': 67}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999753, 'word': 'Atlanta', 'start': 69, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999987, 'word': 'Georgia', 'start': 78, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999763, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 87, 'end': 90}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6931296, 'word': '.', 'start': 90, 'end': 91}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Surgery and Transplantation, Virgen de la Arrixaca University Hospital, Murcia, Spain.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5507486, 'word': 'Department', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.60619104, 'word': 'Sur', 'start': 14, 'end': 17}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8039515, 'word': 'Transplantation', 'start': 26, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9993459, 'word': 'Virgen de la Arrixaca University Hospital', 'start': 43, 'end': 84}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999285, 'word': 'Murcia', 'start': 86, 'end': 92}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999962, 'word': 'Spain', 'start': 94, 'end': 99}",,,,,,,,,
"Specialist Haemostasis Laboratory, Cambridge University Hospitals National Health Service Trust, Cambridge, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.92013854, 'word': 'Specialist Haemostasis Laboratory', 'start': 0, 'end': 33}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9976963, 'word': 'Cambridge University Hospitals National Health Service Trust', 'start': 35, 'end': 95}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999839, 'word': 'Cambridge', 'start': 97, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999607, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 108, 'end': 122}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Cardiology , Texas Heart Institute , Houston , Texas.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998579, 'word': 'Department of Cardiology', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99996597, 'word': 'Texas Heart Institute', 'start': 27, 'end': 48}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999821, 'word': 'Houston', 'start': 51, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998856, 'word': 'Texas', 'start': 61, 'end': 66}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine (Nephrology), Stanford University, Palo Alto, California.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99157625, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9237014, 'word': 'Nephrology', 'start': 24, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99987566, 'word': 'Stanford University', 'start': 37, 'end': 56}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99967563, 'word': 'Palo Alto', 'start': 58, 'end': 67}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999985, 'word': 'California', 'start': 69, 'end': 79}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Rheumatology and Immunology, The Second Xiangya Hospital, Central South University, Changsha, Hunan, China.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.74387336, 'word': 'Department', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.88222164, 'word': 'Rheumatology and Immunology', 'start': 14, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9968363, 'word': 'Second Xiangya Hospital', 'start': 47, 'end': 70}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99917245, 'word': 'Central South University', 'start': 72, 'end': 96}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999805, 'word': 'Changsha', 'start': 98, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999766, 'word': 'Hunan', 'start': 108, 'end': 113}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999926, 'word': 'China', 'start': 115, 'end': 120}",,,,,,,,
"Princess Alexandra Hospital, Woolloongabba.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99985, 'word': 'Princess Alexandra Hospital', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9687198, 'word': 'Woolloongabba.', 'start': 29, 'end': 43}",,,,,,,,,,,,,
"Concord Repatriation General Hospital, Concord, Australia.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9979587, 'word': 'Concord Repatriation General Hospital', 'start': 0, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999094, 'word': 'Concord', 'start': 39, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999714, 'word': 'Australia', 'start': 48, 'end': 57}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Department of Medicine, University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center, Dallas, Texas.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8824399, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7698044, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 24, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96487373, 'word': 'University of Texas', 'start': 48, 'end': 67}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.932171, 'word': 'Southwestern Medical Center', 'start': 68, 'end': 95}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998534, 'word': 'Dallas', 'start': 97, 'end': 103}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999857, 'word': 'Texas', 'start': 105, 'end': 110}",,,,,,,,,
Paris University,"{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999964, 'word': 'Paris University', 'start': 0, 'end': 16}",,,,,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Department of Medicine, Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, Baltimore, MD. Electronic address: chirag.parikh@jhmi.edu.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9827667, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8297989, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 24, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7227886, 'word': 'Johns Hopkins University School of', 'start': 48, 'end': 82}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.76649046, 'word': 'Medicine', 'start': 83, 'end': 91}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999726, 'word': 'Baltimore', 'start': 93, 'end': 102}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99954456, 'word': 'MD', 'start': 104, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9963597, 'word': 'chirag', 'start': 128, 'end': 134}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9955244, 'word': 'parikh', 'start': 135, 'end': 141}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9877362, 'word': 'jhmi', 'start': 142, 'end': 146}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.89590585, 'word': 'edu.', 'start': 147, 'end': 151}",,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Department of Medicine, Duke University, Durham, North Carolina","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9787717, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9700915, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 24, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9988837, 'word': 'Duke University', 'start': 48, 'end': 63}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99991536, 'word': 'Durham', 'start': 65, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999899, 'word': 'North Carolina', 'start': 73, 'end': 87}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Dermatology, Ninewells Hospital and Medical School, Dundee, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.64579046, 'word': 'Department', 'start': 0, 'end': 10}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.88128185, 'word': 'Dermatology', 'start': 14, 'end': 25}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9970296, 'word': 'Ninewells Hospital and Medical School', 'start': 27, 'end': 64}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999628, 'word': 'Dundee', 'start': 66, 'end': 72}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999959, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 74, 'end': 88}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of General Internal Medicine and Hospital Medicine, University of Colorado, Anschutz Medical Campus, Aurora, Colorado.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.91771, 'word': 'Division of General Internal Medicine and Hospital Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99984, 'word': 'University of Colorado', 'start': 61, 'end': 83}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9989954, 'word': 'Anschutz Medical Campus', 'start': 85, 'end': 108}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999857, 'word': 'Aurora', 'start': 110, 'end': 116}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999888, 'word': 'Colorado', 'start': 118, 'end': 126}",,,,,,,,,,
"Glickman Urology and Kidney and Lerner Research Institutes , Cleveland Clinic , and Departments of Molecular Medicine and Physiology and Biophysics , Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland , Ohio.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99938625, 'word': 'Glickman Urology and Kidney and Lerner Research Institutes', 'start': 0, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9980819, 'word': 'Cleveland Clinic', 'start': 61, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96285725, 'word': 'Departments of Molecular Medicine and Physiology and Biophysic', 'start': 84, 'end': 146}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99987483, 'word': 'Case Western Reserve University', 'start': 150, 'end': 181}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99980265, 'word': 'Cleveland', 'start': 183, 'end': 192}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998057, 'word': 'Ohio', 'start': 195, 'end': 199}",,,,,,,,,
"Starzl Transplantation Institute, Department of Surgery and Department of Immunology, University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine, Pittsburgh, PA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999154, 'word': 'Starzl Transplantation Institute', 'start': 0, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9898752, 'word': 'Department of Surgery', 'start': 34, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9960736, 'word': 'Department of Immunology', 'start': 60, 'end': 84}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9935441, 'word': 'University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine', 'start': 86, 'end': 129}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9995266, 'word': 'Pittsburgh', 'start': 131, 'end': 141}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9977157, 'word': 'PA', 'start': 143, 'end': 145}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6712006, 'word': '.', 'start': 145, 'end': 146}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Pediatric Nephrology, Hôpital Trousseau, Paris, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.897387, 'word': 'Department of Pediatric Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.86785483, 'word': 'Hôpital Trousseau', 'start': 36, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999951, 'word': 'Paris', 'start': 55, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999976, 'word': 'France', 'start': 62, 'end': 68}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology and Hypertension, Mayo Clinic, Rochester, MN.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99960995, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology and Hypertension', 'start': 0, 'end': 39}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.983371, 'word': 'Mayo Clinic', 'start': 41, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99994063, 'word': 'Rochester', 'start': 54, 'end': 63}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99957633, 'word': 'MN', 'start': 65, 'end': 67}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Department of Medicine, Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center, University of Alabama at Birmingham, Birmingham, Alabama.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.93277144, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6336805, 'word': 'Department of', 'start': 24, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.74151134, 'word': 'Medicine', 'start': 38, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.98561996, 'word': 'Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center', 'start': 48, 'end': 93}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.95370233, 'word': 'University of Alabama at', 'start': 95, 'end': 119}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.54360163, 'word': 'Birmingham', 'start': 120, 'end': 130}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999583, 'word': 'Birmingham', 'start': 132, 'end': 142}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999985, 'word': 'Alabama', 'start': 144, 'end': 151}",,,,,,,
"Division of Vascular Surgery and Endovascular Therapy, University of Florida, Gainesville, Florida.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96927327, 'word': 'Division of Vascular Surgery and Endovascular Therapy', 'start': 0, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999218, 'word': 'University of Florida', 'start': 55, 'end': 76}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999687, 'word': 'Gainesville', 'start': 78, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999846, 'word': 'Florida', 'start': 91, 'end': 98}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Imperial College Renal and Transplant Centre, Hammersmith Hospital, Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust, London, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.86322004, 'word': 'Imperial College Ren', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.5627805, 'word': 'Trans', 'start': 27, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996257, 'word': 'Hammersmith Hospital', 'start': 46, 'end': 66}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.93792105, 'word': 'Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust', 'start': 68, 'end': 105}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999969, 'word': 'London', 'start': 107, 'end': 113}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999654, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 115, 'end': 129}",,,,,,,,,
"Medical School, University of Western Australia, Perth, Western Australia, Australia","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99916494, 'word': 'Medical School', 'start': 0, 'end': 14}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999948, 'word': 'University of Western Australia', 'start': 16, 'end': 47}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997586, 'word': 'Perth', 'start': 49, 'end': 54}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999917, 'word': 'Western Australia', 'start': 56, 'end': 73}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999924, 'word': 'Australia', 'start': 75, 'end': 84}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Laboratory Medicine and Pathology, University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99788773, 'word': 'Department of Laboratory Medicine and Pathology', 'start': 0, 'end': 47}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999526, 'word': 'University of Minnesota', 'start': 49, 'end': 72}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999063, 'word': 'Minneapolis', 'start': 74, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9996586, 'word': 'MN', 'start': 87, 'end': 89}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Center for Transplantation Sciences, Department of Surgery, Massachusetts General Hospital/Harvard Medical School, Boston, Massachusetts, USA. Electronic address: dkcooper@mgh.harvard.edu.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998378, 'word': 'Center for Transplantation Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 35}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9879487, 'word': 'Department of Surgery', 'start': 37, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.985407, 'word': 'Massachusetts General Hospital/Harvard Medical School', 'start': 60, 'end': 113}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99996984, 'word': 'Boston', 'start': 115, 'end': 121}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999492, 'word': 'Massachusetts', 'start': 123, 'end': 136}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997115, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 138, 'end': 141}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9361895, 'word': 'dkcooper', 'start': 163, 'end': 171}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.902473, 'word': 'mgh', 'start': 172, 'end': 175}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.50327384, 'word': 'harvard', 'start': 176, 'end': 183}",,,,,,
"Department of Public Health Sciences, Penn State College of Medicine, Hershey, Pennsylvania.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9988878, 'word': 'Department of Public Health Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 36}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.98058575, 'word': 'Penn State College of Medicine', 'start': 38, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99803287, 'word': 'Hershey', 'start': 70, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99995005, 'word': 'Pennsylvania', 'start': 79, 'end': 91}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Biotechnology and Methods in Laboratory Medicine, University of Bologna, Bologna.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9994324, 'word': 'University of Bologna', 'start': 50, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99985886, 'word': 'Bologna', 'start': 73, 'end': 80}",,,,,,,,,,,,,
"Sherrie and Alan Conover Center for Liver Disease and Transplantation, Houston Methodist Hospital, Houston, TX.","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.51557857, 'word': 'Sherrie', 'start': 0, 'end': 7}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.5311732, 'word': 'and', 'start': 8, 'end': 11}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.94847375, 'word': 'Alan Conover Center for Liver Disease and Transplantation', 'start': 12, 'end': 69}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99890155, 'word': 'Houston Methodist Hospital', 'start': 71, 'end': 97}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998343, 'word': 'Houston', 'start': 99, 'end': 106}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9997413, 'word': 'TX', 'start': 108, 'end': 110}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Quantitative Health Sciences, Cleveland Clinic, Cleveland, Ohio, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998008, 'word': 'Department of Quantitative Health Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 42}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9918119, 'word': 'Cleveland Clinic', 'start': 44, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9997763, 'word': 'Cleveland', 'start': 62, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999788, 'word': 'Ohio', 'start': 73, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999984, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 79, 'end': 82}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6873166, 'word': '.', 'start': 82, 'end': 83}",,,,,,,,,
"Division of Immunology and Allergy, Department of Paediatrics, the Hospital for Sick Children, Toronto, Ontario, Canada.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99101555, 'word': 'Division of Immunology and Allergy', 'start': 0, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99320734, 'word': 'Department of Paediatrics', 'start': 36, 'end': 61}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99405223, 'word': 'Hospital for Sick Children', 'start': 67, 'end': 93}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999979, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 95, 'end': 102}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999846, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 104, 'end': 111}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999924, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 113, 'end': 119}",,,,,,,,,
"Veterans Affairs San Diego Healthcare System, San Diego, CA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99859965, 'word': 'Veterans Affairs San Diego Healthcare System', 'start': 0, 'end': 44}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998933, 'word': 'San Diego', 'start': 46, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998455, 'word': 'CA', 'start': 57, 'end': 59}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medical Epidemiology and Biostatistics, Karolinska Institute, Stockholm, Sweden.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999509, 'word': 'Department of Medical Epidemiology and Biostatistics', 'start': 0, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999826, 'word': 'Karolinska Institute', 'start': 54, 'end': 74}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99655175, 'word': 'Stockholm', 'start': 76, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999607, 'word': 'Sweden', 'start': 87, 'end': 93}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9509327, 'word': '.', 'start': 93, 'end': 94}",,,,,,,,,,
"Liver Unit, Birmingham Women's and Children's Hospital, Birmingham, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9959409, 'word': ""Birmingham Women's and Children's Hospital"", 'start': 12, 'end': 54}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999831, 'word': 'Birmingham', 'start': 56, 'end': 66}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999955, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 68, 'end': 82}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Global Medical Office, FMC Germany, Bad Homburg, Germany.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9862792, 'word': 'Global Medical Office', 'start': 0, 'end': 21}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99998456, 'word': 'FMC Germany', 'start': 23, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999911, 'word': 'Bad Homburg', 'start': 36, 'end': 47}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999958, 'word': 'Germany', 'start': 49, 'end': 56}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Institute of Health Policy, Management, and Evaluation, University of Toronto, Toronto, Ontario, Canada","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.98873043, 'word': 'Institute of Health Policy, Management, and Evaluation', 'start': 0, 'end': 54}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999819, 'word': 'University of Toronto', 'start': 56, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998847, 'word': 'Toronto', 'start': 79, 'end': 86}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999831, 'word': 'Ontario', 'start': 88, 'end': 95}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999404, 'word': 'Canada', 'start': 97, 'end': 103}",,,,,,,,,,
"School of Exercise and Nutrition Sciences, Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane, Australia","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99907076, 'word': 'School of Exercise and Nutrition Sciences', 'start': 0, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99995834, 'word': 'Queensland University of Technology', 'start': 43, 'end': 78}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998756, 'word': 'Brisbane', 'start': 80, 'end': 88}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999939, 'word': 'Australia', 'start': 90, 'end': 99}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Section of Endocrinology, Department of Internal Medicine, Yale University School of Medicine, New Haven, Connecticut.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99243283, 'word': 'Section of Endocrinology', 'start': 0, 'end': 24}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9893053, 'word': 'Department of Internal Medicine', 'start': 26, 'end': 57}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.96693444, 'word': 'Yale University School of Medicine', 'start': 59, 'end': 93}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999855, 'word': 'New Haven', 'start': 95, 'end': 104}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999819, 'word': 'Connecticut', 'start': 106, 'end': 117}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Nephrology, Department of Internal Medicine, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9921363, 'word': 'Division of Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99552375, 'word': 'Department of Internal Medicine', 'start': 24, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998123, 'word': 'University of Michigan', 'start': 57, 'end': 79}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999793, 'word': 'Ann Arbor', 'start': 81, 'end': 90}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999571, 'word': 'Michigan', 'start': 92, 'end': 100}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, Houston Methodist Hospital, Houston, Texas.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9998628, 'word': 'Houston Methodist Hospital', 'start': 24, 'end': 50}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999285, 'word': 'Houston', 'start': 52, 'end': 59}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999807, 'word': 'Texas', 'start': 61, 'end': 66}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"UT Southwestern Medical Center, Dallas, Texas, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9446638, 'word': 'UT', 'start': 0, 'end': 2}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9622227, 'word': 'Southwestern Medical Center', 'start': 3, 'end': 30}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999856, 'word': 'Dallas', 'start': 32, 'end': 38}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999856, 'word': 'Texas', 'start': 40, 'end': 45}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998987, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 47, 'end': 50}",,,,,,,,,,
"Division of Renal Pathology, Department of Pathology, The Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, Baltimore, Maryland.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.98860097, 'word': 'Division of Renal Pathology', 'start': 0, 'end': 27}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.97693914, 'word': 'Department of Pathology', 'start': 29, 'end': 52}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.81541395, 'word': 'Johns Hopkins University School of', 'start': 58, 'end': 92}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.73497, 'word': 'Medicine', 'start': 93, 'end': 101}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998164, 'word': 'Baltimore', 'start': 103, 'end': 112}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997663, 'word': 'Maryland', 'start': 114, 'end': 122}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Nephrology and Rheumatology, University Medical Center Göttingen, Germany.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99147564, 'word': 'Department of Nephrology and Rheumatology', 'start': 0, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.78732854, 'word': 'University Medical Center Göttingen', 'start': 43, 'end': 78}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999607, 'word': 'Germany', 'start': 80, 'end': 87}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, University of California San Francisco at the Priscilla Chan and Mark Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital, San Francisco, CA","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9956086, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999651, 'word': 'University of California San Francisco', 'start': 24, 'end': 62}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.934137, 'word': 'Pris', 'start': 70, 'end': 74}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.838188, 'word': 'cilla Chan', 'start': 74, 'end': 84}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.91672844, 'word': 'and Mark Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital', 'start': 85, 'end': 135}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99993944, 'word': 'San Francisco', 'start': 137, 'end': 150}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99955934, 'word': 'CA', 'start': 152, 'end': 154}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Infectious Diseases, Hospital Clinic - IDIBAPS, University of Barcelona, Barcelona, Spain.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99947274, 'word': 'Department of Infectious Diseases', 'start': 0, 'end': 33}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998374, 'word': 'IDIBAPS', 'start': 53, 'end': 60}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999834, 'word': 'University of Barcelona', 'start': 62, 'end': 85}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999972, 'word': 'Barcelona', 'start': 87, 'end': 96}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999997, 'word': 'Spain', 'start': 98, 'end': 103}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.7310066, 'word': '.', 'start': 103, 'end': 104}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of General Internal Medicine, Medical Intensive Care Unit, UZ Leuven, Leuven, Belgium.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8242861, 'word': 'UZ Leuven', 'start': 70, 'end': 79}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999941, 'word': 'Leuven', 'start': 81, 'end': 87}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999938, 'word': 'Belgium', 'start': 89, 'end': 96}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Lineberger Comprehensive Cancer Center, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, USA","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.8266608, 'word': 'Lineberger Comprehen', 'start': 0, 'end': 20}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.7437116, 'word': 'Cancer Center', 'start': 25, 'end': 38}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9779814, 'word': 'University of North Carolina at', 'start': 40, 'end': 71}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9591576, 'word': 'Chapel Hill', 'start': 72, 'end': 83}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999022, 'word': 'Chapel Hill', 'start': 85, 'end': 96}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999634, 'word': 'North Carolina', 'start': 98, 'end': 112}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999941, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 114, 'end': 117}",,,,,,,,
"Department of Surgery, Duke Transplant Center, Duke University School of Medicine, Duke Clinical Research Institute, Durham, North Carolina, USA. Electronic address: stuart.knechtle@duke.edu.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9893613, 'word': 'Department of Surgery', 'start': 0, 'end': 21}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9878297, 'word': 'Duke Transplant Center', 'start': 23, 'end': 45}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8776781, 'word': 'Duke University School of Medicine', 'start': 47, 'end': 81}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9981562, 'word': 'Duke Clinical Research Institute', 'start': 83, 'end': 115}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999758, 'word': 'Durham', 'start': 117, 'end': 123}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998534, 'word': 'North Carolina', 'start': 125, 'end': 139}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99997234, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 141, 'end': 144}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9221296, 'word': 'stuart.knechtle', 'start': 166, 'end': 181}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99058247, 'word': 'duke', 'start': 182, 'end': 186}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.8716077, 'word': 'edu', 'start': 187, 'end': 190}",,,,,
"UNC Blood Research Center, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, North Carolina","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998849, 'word': 'UNC Blood Research Center', 'start': 0, 'end': 25}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9300591, 'word': 'University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill', 'start': 27, 'end': 70}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999584, 'word': 'Chapel Hill', 'start': 72, 'end': 83}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999908, 'word': 'North Carolina', 'start': 85, 'end': 99}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Immunology, Genetics and Pathology, Section of Clinical Immunology, Uppsala University, Sweden. Electronic address: david.berglund@itb-med.com.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999076, 'word': 'Department of Immunology, Genetics and Pathology', 'start': 0, 'end': 48}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99754095, 'word': 'Section of Clinical Immunology', 'start': 50, 'end': 80}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998821, 'word': 'Uppsala University', 'start': 82, 'end': 100}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999958, 'word': 'Sweden', 'start': 102, 'end': 108}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9993708, 'word': 'david', 'start': 130, 'end': 135}","{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99890494, 'word': 'berglund', 'start': 136, 'end': 144}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.97081065, 'word': 'itb-med.com', 'start': 145, 'end': 156}",,,,,,,,
"LIM 03, Division of Clinical Pathology, University of São Paulo Medical School, São Paulo, Brazil.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.49834895, 'word': '', 'start': 0, 'end': 1}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.77861196, 'word': 'Division of Clinic', 'start': 8, 'end': 26}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.91991025, 'word': 'Pathology', 'start': 29, 'end': 38}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9946429, 'word': 'University of São Paulo Medical School', 'start': 40, 'end': 78}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999464, 'word': 'São Paulo', 'start': 80, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999225, 'word': 'Brazil', 'start': 91, 'end': 97}",,,,,,,,,
"Department of Pathology, UZ Leuven, Leuven, Belgium.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99980944, 'word': 'UZ Leuven', 'start': 25, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999404, 'word': 'Leuven', 'start': 36, 'end': 42}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999945, 'word': 'Belgium', 'start': 44, 'end': 51}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Family Medicine, La Maestra Community Health Centers, San Diego, California.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.93028516, 'word': 'Department of Family Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 29}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9986467, 'word': 'La Maestra', 'start': 31, 'end': 41}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999818, 'word': 'San Diego', 'start': 68, 'end': 77}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999871, 'word': 'California', 'start': 79, 'end': 89}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Travere Therapeutics, Inc., San Diego, California.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.999877, 'word': 'Travere Therapeutics, Inc.', 'start': 0, 'end': 26}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998766, 'word': 'San Diego', 'start': 28, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999926, 'word': 'California', 'start': 39, 'end': 49}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9251659, 'word': '.', 'start': 49, 'end': 50}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Service de Néphrologie et Immunologie Clinique, CHU Nantes, Nantes, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9993654, 'word': 'Service de Néphrologie et Immunologie Clinique', 'start': 0, 'end': 46}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9918567, 'word': 'CHU Nantes', 'start': 48, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999932, 'word': 'Nantes', 'start': 60, 'end': 66}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999974, 'word': 'France', 'start': 68, 'end': 74}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, King Khalid University Hospital, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99990916, 'word': 'King Khalid University Hospital', 'start': 24, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999726, 'word': 'Riyadh', 'start': 57, 'end': 63}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999756, 'word': 'Saudi Arabia', 'start': 65, 'end': 77}",,,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Medicine, University of Nebraska Medical Center, Omaha, Nebraska, USA.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.70540094, 'word': 'Department of Medicine', 'start': 0, 'end': 22}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.75339925, 'word': 'University of', 'start': 24, 'end': 37}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.7879204, 'word': 'Nebraska Medical Center', 'start': 38, 'end': 61}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999803, 'word': 'Omaha', 'start': 63, 'end': 68}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999841, 'word': 'Nebraska', 'start': 70, 'end': 78}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999825, 'word': 'USA', 'start': 80, 'end': 83}",,,,,,,,,
"Microbiology Department, La Paz University Hospital Institute for Health Research (IdiPAZ), CIBERINFEC, Carlos III Health Institute, Madrid, Spain.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.76312554, 'word': 'Microbiology Department', 'start': 0, 'end': 23}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6132576, 'word': 'La', 'start': 25, 'end': 27}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.70731395, 'word': 'Paz', 'start': 28, 'end': 31}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.85181147, 'word': 'University Hospital Institute for Health Research', 'start': 32, 'end': 81}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9984807, 'word': 'IdiPAZ', 'start': 83, 'end': 89}","{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.8599388, 'word': 'BERINFE', 'start': 94, 'end': 101}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9638825, 'word': 'Carlos III Health Institute', 'start': 104, 'end': 131}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99998593, 'word': 'Madrid', 'start': 133, 'end': 139}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999975, 'word': 'Spain', 'start': 141, 'end': 146}",,,,,,
"University of Utah Health and VA Salt Lake City Health Care System, Salt Lake City, Utah.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99136335, 'word': 'University of Utah Health and VA', 'start': 0, 'end': 32}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99384147, 'word': 'Salt Lake City Health Care System', 'start': 33, 'end': 66}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999959, 'word': 'Salt Lake City', 'start': 68, 'end': 82}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999884, 'word': 'Utah', 'start': 84, 'end': 88}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Dermatology, Medical University of Vienna, Vienna, Austria.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9653789, 'word': 'Department of Dermatology', 'start': 0, 'end': 25}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999424, 'word': 'Medical University of Vienna', 'start': 27, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999691, 'word': 'Vienna', 'start': 57, 'end': 63}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999957, 'word': 'Austria', 'start': 65, 'end': 72}",,,,,,,,,,,
"Aliasghar Children's Hospital, Department of Pediatrics, School of Medicine, Iran University of Medical Sciences, Tehran, Iran.","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9900569, 'word': ""Aliasghar Children's Hospital"", 'start': 0, 'end': 29}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.6756965, 'word': 'Pediatrics', 'start': 45, 'end': 55}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.77273417, 'word': 'School of Medicine', 'start': 57, 'end': 75}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999182, 'word': 'Iran University of Medical Sciences', 'start': 77, 'end': 112}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999927, 'word': 'Tehran', 'start': 114, 'end': 120}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999344, 'word': 'Iran', 'start': 122, 'end': 126}",,,,,,,,,
"UK Renal Registry, The UK Kidney Association, Bristol, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99999523, 'word': 'UK Renal Registry', 'start': 0, 'end': 17}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9997333, 'word': 'The UK Kidney Association', 'start': 19, 'end': 44}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999629, 'word': 'Bristol', 'start': 46, 'end': 53}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.999997, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 55, 'end': 69}",,,,,,,,,,,
"MRC Population Health Research Unit, Clinical Trial Service Unit and Epidemiological Studies Unit, University of Oxford, Oxford, United Kingdom.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.97369695, 'word': 'MRC Population Health Research Unit, Clinical Trial Service Unit and Epidemiological Studies Unit', 'start': 0, 'end': 97}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9998991, 'word': 'University of Oxford', 'start': 99, 'end': 119}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99710363, 'word': 'Oxford', 'start': 121, 'end': 127}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999956, 'word': 'United Kingdom', 'start': 129, 'end': 143}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.83314115, 'word': '.', 'start': 143, 'end': 144}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Surgery, Seoul National University Hospital and Seoul National University College of Medicine, Seoul, South Korea.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.91417265, 'word': 'Department of Surgery', 'start': 0, 'end': 21}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9173382, 'word': 'Seoul National University Hospital', 'start': 23, 'end': 57}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99680024, 'word': 'Seoul National University College of Medicine', 'start': 62, 'end': 107}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999949, 'word': 'Seoul', 'start': 109, 'end': 114}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999356, 'word': 'South Korea', 'start': 116, 'end': 127}",,,,,,,,,,
"Department of Physiology and Pathophysiology, School of Basic Medical Sciences, Peking University, Key Laboratory of Molecular Cardiovascular Science, Ministry of Education, Beijing, China.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99396783, 'word': 'Department of Physiology and Pathophysiology', 'start': 0, 'end': 44}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9997472, 'word': 'School of Basic Medical Sciences', 'start': 46, 'end': 78}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9999831, 'word': 'Peking University', 'start': 80, 'end': 97}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9987197, 'word': 'Key Laboratory of Molecular Cardiovascular Science', 'start': 99, 'end': 149}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99997014, 'word': 'Ministry of Education', 'start': 151, 'end': 172}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99989533, 'word': 'Beijing', 'start': 174, 'end': 181}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99999416, 'word': 'China', 'start': 183, 'end': 188}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.989776, 'word': '.', 'start': 188, 'end': 189}",,,,,,,
"Department of Pediatric Nephrology, CHU Besançon, Besançon, France.","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9842987, 'word': 'Department of Pediatric Nephrology', 'start': 0, 'end': 34}","{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.90199625, 'word': 'CHU Besançon', 'start': 36, 'end': 48}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999933, 'word': 'Besançon', 'start': 50, 'end': 58}","{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9999975, 'word': 'France', 'start': 60, 'end': 66}",,,,,,,,,,,
